A Guide to the Virginia Newspaper Collection, 1861-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Virginia Newspaper Collection, 1861-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2012-034
20 Cubic Feet 16 boxes
The collection contains individual or groups of issues of Virginia newspapers, organized by location and dating from the 1860s-1990s.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The newspapers in this collection have been donated to Special Collections over time. Additional materials may be added in the future.
Other Finding Aids
A spreadsheet with information about specific holdings (titles, dates, volume and issue numbers, cities/towns of publication, and, when available, cost and editors) can be downloaded here. The spreadsheets allows for easy sorting by any category.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of individual issues of Virginia newspapers. In some cases, this is a single issue; in other cases, there may be multiple issues. Newspapers represent cities and towns throughout the Commonwealth and date from the start of the Civil War up through the 1990s.
Arrangement
The physical collection is arranged alphabetically by city or town. The contents list below is organized by city or town and contains a list of paper titles in each box. The city or town of origination is included with the title. Under each title is a list of holdings. The general format is "date, volume, issue number." Some titles may only list dates or dates and volumes.
For ease of searching, a downloadable spreadsheet which can be sorted by city/town, title, date, issue, and other known information, can be found here.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Virginia -- History
Contents List
- Box 1: Alexandria-Cape Charles (Box 1)
  - Alexandria Times (The), Alexandria, VA
    - 05/29/1897, III, 788
  - Amherst New Era (The), Amherst, VA
    - 06/13/1901, XXI, 21
  - Blacksburg Banner (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 11/17/1938-12/09/1938, v.1 no.1- vol.1 no.4
  - Blacksburg Chronicle (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 8/1/1945
    - 8/29/1945
    - 9/12/1945
  - Blacksburg Citizen (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 05/1943-06/1945, v.1 no.1-v.3 no.1
  - Blacksburg News, Blacksburg, VA
    - 06/06/1907, XI, 3
    - 08/25/1910, XIII, 40
  - Blacksburg Sun (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 03/22/1972, Centennial Edition
  - Blacksburg Virginian (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 04/03/1950, I, 1
  - Cape Charles Light (The), Cape Charles, VA
    - 12/15/1898-12/22/1898, v.IX no.49-v.IX no.50
  - Courier Record, Blacksburg, VA
    - 04/27/1972, 83, 17
  - Farmville Herald (The), Appomattox, VA
    - 4/6/1961
  - Home News, Blacksburg, VA
    - 09/02/1916, I, 1
  - Little Citizen (The) (Blacksburg Elementary School), Blacksburg, VA
    - 1949-1950, XI
  - Plain Dealer (The), Blacksburg, VA
    - 01/1976-03/1976, v.1. no.1-v.1 no.4
  - Roanoke Valley (The), Boydton, VA
    - 06/08/1875, 3, 32
  - Tattle Tale (The) (Blacksburg High School), Blacksburg, VA
    - 10/1972-02/1928, v.1 no.1-v.1 no.5
    - 04/01/1928, v.1 no.7-v.3 no. 6, 7
    - 4/19/1905
    - 04/29/1905, Annual
    - 04/30/1905
    - 04/01/1947
    - 05/01/1947
  - Town and Campus (Published by the Blacksburg Sun), Blacksburg, VA
    - 1967-68 Guide, I
    - 1968-69 Guide, II
    - 1969-1970 Guide, III
    - 1971-1972 Guide, IV
- Box 2: Christiansburg (Box 2)
  - Montgomery Free Press, Christiansburg, VA
    - 03/18/1976-09/30/1976, 1, no. 1-29
    - 10/07/1976-12/16/1976, 1, no. 31-41
    - 01/06/1977-02/24/1977, 2, no. 1- 8
  - Montgomery Messenger (The), Christiansburg, VA
    - 01/06/1916- 06/02/1916, v.XLVIII no.1- v.XLVIII no.21
    - 06/09/1916-11/10/1916, v. XLVIII no.23- v.XLVIII no.45
    - 11/17/1916-12/21/1917, v.XLVIII no.47- v.XLIX no.51
    - 01/12/1918-08/02/1918, v.L no.2-v.L no.30
  - Montgomery Messenger, Christiansburg, VA
    - 01/05/1870-01/12/1870, 1, no. 6-7
    - 03/02/1870, 1, 14
    - 03/16/1870, 1, 16
    - 07/06/1870, 1, 32
    - 10/14/1870, 1, 46
    - 12/02/1870-12/09/1870, 2, no. 1-2
    - 02/24/1871, 2, 12
    - 05/12/1871, 2, 23
    - 07/28/1871, 2, 34
    - 09/02/1871, 2, 40
    - 09/22/1871-10/06/1871, 2, 42-44
    - 10/20/1871, 2, 46
    - 11/03/1871-11/24/1871, 2, 48-51
    - 12/08/1871-12/15/1871, 3, no. 1-2
    - 07/05/1872, 3, 29
    - 10/04/1872-10/11/1872, 3, 43-44
    - 10/25/1872-11/01/1872, 3, 46-47
    - 02/07/1873, 4, 8
    - 05/06/1873, 4, 25
    - 07/02/1875-07/09/1875, 4, 27-28
    - 05/02/1876, 7, 23
    - 01/05/1877, 8, 1
    - 03/09/1877, 8, 9
    - 07/27/1877, 8, 29
    - 01/25/1878, 9, 3
    - 10/04/1878-10/11/1878, 9, 39-40
    - 01/10/1879-02/21/1879, 10, no.1-6
    - 03/07/1879, 10, 9
    - 05/02/1879-06/13/1879, 10, 17-23
    - 07/18/1879-08/01/1879, 10, 28-30
    - 02/20/1880, 11, 7
    - 03/12/1880, 11, 10
    - 04/02/1880, 11, 13
    - 08/13/1880, 11, 32
    - 12/24/1880, 11, 50
    - 02/04/1881, 12, 4
    - 03/18/1881, 12, 10
    - 04/01/1881, 12, 12
    - 12/02/1881, 12, 47
    - 09/14/1883, 14, 37
    - 02/04/1887-02/25/1887, 18, no. 5-8
    - 03/18/1887-05/24/1887, 18, no. 11-25
    - 07/15/1887-12/16/1887, 18, 28-50
    - 04/24/1891-05/01/1891, 22, 17-18
    - 06/05/1891, 22, 23
    - 04/22/1892, 23, 16
    - 02/08/1895, 27, 1
    - 05/31/1895, 27, 16
    - 07/26/1895, 27, 23
    - 08/23/1895, 27, 27
    - 06/12/1896, 28, 16
    - 10/30/1896, 28, 36
    - 06/04/1897, 29, 21
    - 07/09/1897, 29, 26
    - 08/27/1897, 29, 33
    - 09/03/1897, 29, 33
    - 10/22/1897, 29, 40
    - 11/05/1897, 29, 42
    - 11/26/1897, 29, 44
    - 01/21/1898-02/04/1898, XXX, no. 3-5
    - 03/11/1898, XXX, 11
    - 05/27/1898, XXX, 22
    - 09/09/1898-09/23/1898, XXX, 36-37
    - 11/25/1898-12/02/1898, XXX, 46-47
    - 12/16/1898-12/23/1898, XXX, 50-51
    - 01/27/1899-02/10/1899, XXXI, no. 4-6
    - 03/03/1899-03/24/1899, XXXI, no. 9-12
    - 04/21/1899, XXXI, 16
    - 05/12/1899-05/19/1899, XXXI, 19-20
    - 07/28/1899-08/04/1899, XXXI, 27-28
    - 08/18/1899-09/08/1899, XXXI, 30-33
    - 09/26/1899, XXXI, 39
    - 10/27/1899-11/03/1899, XXXI, 43-44
    - 11/24/1899-12/01/1899, XXXI, 47-48
    - 01/05/1900, XXXII, 1
    - 01/19/1900, XXXII, 3
    - 02/02/1900, XXXII, 5
    - 3/9/1900-3/30/1900, XXXII, no. 9-12
    - 4/13/1900-05/18/1900, XXXII, 14-19
    - 6/1/1900-07/20/1900, XXXII, 21-28
    - 8/31/1900-09/07/1900, XXXII, 34-35
    - 10/19/1900-10/26/1900, XXXII, 41-42
    - 11/9/1900- 11/23/1900, XXXII, 45-46
    - 01/27/1907, XXXVIIII, 4
    - 01/11/1901, XXXIII, 2
    - 01/25/1901, XXXIII, 4
    - 02/01/1901, XXXIII, 9
    - 03/15/1901, XXXIII, 11
    - 3/29/1901-4/12/1901, XXXIII, 13-15
    - 4/26/1901-5/03/1901, XXXIII, 18-19
    - 5/24/1901-6/07/1901, XXXIII, 22-24
    - 06/28/1901, XXXIII, 27
    - 7/12/1901-7/19/1901, XXXIII, 29-30
    - 8/2/1901-8/9/1901, XXXIII, 32-33
    - 08/30/1901, XXXIII, 36
    - 09/13/1901, XXXIII, 38
    - 09/27/1901, XXXIII, 40
    - 10/11/1901, XXXIII, 42
    - 8/8/1902-08/15/1902, XXXIV, 32-33
    - 01/09/1903, XXXV, 1
    - 03/13/1903, XXXV, 11
    - 03/04/1904, XXXVI, 9
    - 04/15/1904, XXXVI, 15
    - 7/18/1904-7/15/1904, XXXVI, 26-27
    - 07/29/1904, XXXVI, 30
    - 09/23/1904, XXXVI, 38
    - 10/07/1904, XXXVI, 40
    - 11/11/1904, XXXVI, 45
    - 02/03/1905, XXXVII, 5
    - 12/08/1905, XXXVII, 49
    - 04/20/1906, XXXVIII, 17
    - 11/30/1906-12/21/1906, XXXVIII, 48-51
    - 01/18/1907, XXXVIIII, 3
    - 02/08/1907, XXXVIIII, no.g
    - 02/15/1907, XXXVIIII, 7
    - 04/05/1907, XXXVIIII, 14
    - 5/10/1907-05/24/1907, XXXVIIII, 19-21
    - 07/05/1907, XXXVIIII, 27
    - 09/27/1907, XXXVIIII, 39
    - 11/01/1907, XXXVIIII, 44
    - 04/03/1908, XI, 14
    - 08/27/1909, XLI, 34
    - 12/02/1910, XLII, 47
    - 05/09/1911, XLIII, 23
    - 12/08/1911, XLIII, 48
    - 04/26/1912
    - 02/14/1913, XLV, 7
    - 09/05/1913, XLV, 36
    - 07/24/1914, XLVI, 30
    - 08/20/1915, XLVII, 34
    - 09/10/1915, XLVII, 37
  - Montgomery News, Christiansburg, VA
    - 09/24/1926, 2, 38
    - 11/26/1926, 2, 47
    - 11/11/1927, 3, 45
    - 11/16/1926, 62, 46
  - Montgomery News Messenger, Christiansburg, VA
    - 05/30/1957, v.91 no.37
- Box 3: Christiansburg-Floyd (Box 3)
  - Charlotte Gazette (The), Drakes Branch, VA
    - 08/03/1972, 99, 40
  - Floyd Press (The), Floyd, VA
    - 06/06/1940, 40, 23
    - 08/21/1941, 46
    - 06/08/1949, 59, 23
    - 07/27/1950, 59, 30
    - 01/18/1951, 60, 3
    - 02/15/1951, 60, 7
    - 02/22/1951, 60, 8
    - 08/09/1951, 60, 32
    - 08/16/1951, 60, 33
    - 10/18/1952, 60, 42
    - 5/1/1952- 5/29/1952, 62, 17-21
    - 06/19/1952, 62, 24
    - 8/7/1952-08/21/1952, 63, 29-30
    - 04/08/1954, 64, 14
    - 5/6/1954-05/13/1954, 64, 18-19
    - 5/27/1954-06/24/1954, 64, 21-25
    - 07/15/1954-08/05/1954, 64, 28-31
    - 02/03/1955, 65, 3
    - 2/10/1955-02/24/1955, 65, no.6-8
    - 06/16/1955, 64, 24-46
    - 12/08/1955, 64, 48
    - 12/22/1955, 64, 51
    - 01/05/1956, 65, 1
    - 1/26/1956-02/09/1956, no. 3-4
    - 02/16/1956, 7
    - 03/08/1956, 10
    - 3/22/1956-03/29/1956, no.12-13
    - 07/26/1956, 29
    - 12/20/1956, 51
    - 04/11/1957, 66, 15
    - 07/04/1957, 27
    - 10/02/1958, 67, 40
    - 02/12/1959, 69, 7
    - 03/12/1959, 11
    - 3/26/1959-05/21/1959, 13-21
    - 09/01/1960, 70, 35
    - 12/01/1960, 70, 48
    - 12/28/1961, 70, 51
    - 01/05/1961, 71, 1
    - 07/01/1976, 85, 26
    - 7/23/1981-09/10/1981, 90, 30-37
  - Southside Virginia News (The) (supplement-4-H Club 50th Anniversary Edition), Dinwiddie County, VA
    - 01/00/1900, 1, 1
  - Southwest (The), Christiansburg, VA
    - 03/23/1867, 1, 8
    - 04/13/1867, 1, 10
    - 04/27/1867-05/11/1867, 1, 13-15
    - 11/02/1867, 1, 39
    - 04/25/1868-05/16/1868, 2, no. 12-15
    - 07/25/1868, 2, 25
    - 09/26/1868, 2, 34
    - 10/17/1868, 2, 37
    - 10/24/1868, 2, 38
    - 01/02/1869, 2, 47
  - Twice-A-Week Register (The), Danville, VA
    - 07/23/1905
  - Virginia Star (The), Culpeper, VA
    - 02/14/1952
- Box 15: Clintwood (Box 15)
  - Cumberland Times (The), Clintwood, VA
    - 01/18/1985, 18, 14
    - 02/15/1989, 22, 15
    - 02/22/1989, 22, 47
    - 10/04/1989, 22, 13
    - 02/14/1990, 23, 25
    - 07/18/1990, 23, 29
    - 08/15/1990, 23, 50
    - 10/31/1990, 23
    - 12/05/1990, 24
    - 05/08/1991, 24
    - 05/22/1991, 24
    - 05/29/1991, 24
    - 01/01/1992, 25, 13
    - 02/26/1992, 25, 17
    - 03/25/1992, 25, 18
    - 04/01/1992, 25, 23
    - 05/06/1992, 25, 25
    - 05/20/1992, 25, 26
    - 05/27/1992, 25, 30
    - 06/24/1992, 25
- Box 4: Floyd-Lynchburg (Not Lebanon) (Box 4)
  - Brunswick Gazette, Lawrenceville, Brusnwick County, VA
    - 02/07/1901, XII, 3
  - Daily News-Record, Harrisonburg, VA
    - 08/04/1932, LXXII, 74
  - Floyd Reporter (The), Floyd, VA
    - 05/08/1885, 12, 31
  - Gazette and Banner, Lexington, VA
    - 05/16/1866, I, 11
  - Hampton Monitor (The), Hampton, VA
    - 08/07/1901, XXV, 34
  - Lynchburg Daily News (The Daily News), Lynchburg, VA
    - 05/09/1873, XV, 99
    - 06/04/1873
    - 08/19/1873, XVI, 30
    - 09/24/1873, XVI, 60
    - 02/04/1874, XVII, 18
    - 03/23/1874, 58
    - 06/06/1874, 123
    - 09/29/1874, XVIII, 66
    - 12/24/1874, 139
    - 04/05/1878, XXV, 68
    - 08/24/1878, XXVI, 34
    - 08/27/1878, 36
    - 06/11/1880, XXIX, 136
    - 06/25/1880, XXX, 5
    - 07/09/1880, 16
    - 07/28/1880, 30
    - 12/11/1880, 146
    - 01/20/1881, XXXI, 5
    - 02/04/1881, 18
    - 03/15/1881, 51
    - 07/07/1881, 147
    - 08/05/1881, XXXII, 19
    - 08/13/1881, 26
    - 10/25/1881, XXXIII, 88
    - 11/05/1881, XXXIII, 98
    - 11/11/1881, 103
    - 12/14/1881, 130
    - 07/25/1882, XXXIV, 8
    - 07/13/1884, 168
    - 03/28/1885, XXXIX, 63
    - 07/03/1886, 41, 145
    - 12/25/1886, 294
    - 03/10/1887, XIV, 9
    - 08/11/1889, 47, 176
    - 11/23/1889, 46, 106
  - News (The), Lynchburg, VA
    - 12/25/1896
    - 10/14/1959
  - Peoples' Advocate (The), Hillsville, Caroll County, VA
    - 11/11/1897, 17
  - Tri-Weekly News (The), Lynchburg, VA
    - 10/18/1872, VII, 120
    - 10/21/1872, 121
    - 01/13/1873, 314
- Boxes 5-7: Lebanon (Box 5, Box 6, Box 7)
  - Lebanon News, Lebanon, Russell County, VA
    - 01/05/1900
    - 02/09/1900
    - 03/09/1900
    - 03/16/1900
    - 03/23/1900
    - 04/06/1900
    - 04/13/1900
    - 05/04/1900
    - 05/11/1900
    - 06/01/1900
    - 06/08/1900
    - 06/15/1900
    - 06/29/1900
    - 08/10/1900
    - 08/24/1900
    - 10/05/1900
    - 11/30/1900
    - 01/02/1903
    - 01/16/1903
    - 01/23/1903
    - 02/13/1903
    - 03/06/1903
    - 03/13/1903
    - 03/20/1903
    - 03/27/1903
    - 04/03/1903
    - 04/01/1903
    - 04/17/1903
    - 05/01/1903
    - 05/08/1903
    - 05/29/1903
    - 05/05/1903
    - 06/12/1903
    - 07/10/1903
    - 07/17/1903
    - 07/24/1903
    - 07/31/1903
    - 08/07/1903
    - 08/14/1903
    - 08/21/1903
    - 08/28/1903
    - 09/04/1903
    - 09/11/1903
    - 09/18/1903
    - 09/25/1903
    - 10/02/1903
    - 10/16/1903
    - 10/23/1903
    - 11/27/1903
    - 12/04/1903
    - 12/18/1903
    - 01/08/1904
    - 01/15/1904
    - 01/29/1904
    - 03/18/1904
    - 07/01/1904
    - 07/08/1904
    - 07/15/1904
    - 11/25/1904
    - 12/02/1904
    - 12/23/1904
    - 03/10/1905
    - 03/31/1905
    - 04/28/1905
    - 06/09/1905
    - 06/09/1905
    - 06/16/1905
    - 07/14/1905
    - 07/21/1905
    - 02/02/1906
    - 02/23/1906
    - 03/16/1906
    - 04/06/1906
    - 04/13/1906
    - 08/03/1906
    - 08/10/1906
    - 08/17/1906
    - 01/11/1907
    - 01/25/1907
    - 02/01/1907
    - 03/08/1907
    - 05/10/1907
    - 06/21/1907
    - 07/05/1907
    - 07/19/1907
    - 07/26/1907
    - 08/02/1907
    - 08/23/1907
    - 08/30/1907
    - 09/06/1907
    - 09/13/1907
    - 09/27/1907
    - 10/11/1907
    - 10/25/1907
    - 11/01/1907
    - 11/22/1907
    - 01/17/1908
    - 01/23/1908
    - 02/28/1908
    - 03/06/1908
    - 03/13/1908
    - 04/03/1908
    - 05/01/1908
    - 05/15/1908
    - 05/29/1908
    - 06/05/1908
    - 06/19/1908
    - 07/03/1908
    - 07/24/1908
    - 08/14/1908
    - 10/09/1908
    - 10/23/1908
    - 10/31/1908
    - 11/27/1908
    - 12/25/1908
    - 01/08/1908
    - 01/15/1909
    - 02/12/1909
    - 02/26/1909
    - 03/05/1909
    - 03/12/1909
    - 03/26/1909
    - 04/12/1909
    - 04/09/1909
    - 04/23/1909
    - 05/07/1909
    - 05/14/1900
    - 05/21/1909
    - 05/28/1909
    - 06/11/1909
    - 06/25/1909
    - 07/09/1909
    - 07/16/1909
    - 07/23/1909
    - 07/30/1909
    - 08/06/1909
    - 08/13/1909
    - 08/27/1909
    - 09/17/1909
    - 10/01/1909
    - 10/08/1909
    - 10/15/1909
    - 10/29/1909
    - 11/05/1909
    - 11/12/1909
    - 11/26/1909
    - 12/03/1909
    - 12/10/1909
    - 12/17/1909
    - 12/24/1909
    - 01/07/1909
    - 01/14/1910
    - 01/21/1910
    - 02/11/1910
    - 02/18/1910
    - 02/25/1910
    - 03/04/1910
    - 03/18/1910
    - 03/25/1910
    - 04/15/1910
    - 04/22/1910
    - 05/06/1910
    - 05/13/1910
    - 05/20/1910
    - 05/27/1910
    - 05/10/1910
    - 07/08/1910
    - 07/15/1910
    - 08/19/1910
    - 08/26/1910
    - 09/16/1910
    - 09/23/1910
    - 11/21/1910
    - 11/04/1910
    - 12/16/1910
    - 01/06/1911
    - 01/13/1911
    - 01/20/1911
    - 01/27/1911
    - 02/03/1911
    - 02/10/1911
    - 03/03/1911
    - 03/17/1911
    - 03/24/1911
    - 04/07/1911
    - 04/21/1911
    - 05/05/1911
    - 05/19/1911
    - 05/26/1911
    - 06/02/1911
    - 05/09/1911
    - 06/16/1911
    - 07/14/1911
    - 07/21/1911
    - 07/28/1911
    - 08/04/1911
    - 08/18/1911
    - 08/25/1911
    - 09/15/1911
    - 09/22/1911
    - 09/29/1911
    - 10/13/1911
    - 10/20/1911
    - 10/27/1911
    - 11/10/1911
    - 11/17/1911
    - 11/24/1911
    - 12/08/1911
    - 02/12/1912
    - 01/19/1912
    - 01/26/1912
    - 02/02/1912
    - 02/09/1912
    - 02/16/1912
    - 02/23/1912
    - 03/08/1912
    - 03/15/1912
    - 03/29/1912
    - 04/05/1912
    - 04/12/1912
    - 04/19/1912
    - 05/03/1912
    - 05/10/1912
    - 05/17/1912
    - 05/31/1912
    - 06/07/1912
    - 06/14/1912
    - 06/21/1912
    - 06/28/1912
    - 07/12/1912
    - 07/26/1912
    - 08/09/1912
    - 08/16/1912
    - 08/23/1912
    - 08/30/1912
    - 09/06/1912
    - 09/13/1912
    - 09/20/1912
    - 10/04/1912
    - 10/18/1912
    - 11/29/1912
    - 12/06/1912
    - 12/13/1912
    - 12/20/1912
    - 01/03/1913
    - 01/10/1913
    - 01/24/1913
    - 02/07/1913
    - 02/14/1913
    - 03/07/1913
    - 03/14/1913
    - 03/21/1913
    - 03/28/1913
    - 04/04/1913
    - 04/11/1913
    - 04/18/1913
    - 04/25/1913
    - 05/23/1913
    - 05/30/1913
    - 06/06/1913
    - 06/13/1913
    - 06/27/1913
    - 07/04/1913
    - 07/11/1913
    - 07/18/1913
    - 07/25/1913
    - 08/08/1913
    - 08/15/1913
    - 08/22/1913
    - 09/05/1913
    - 09/12/1913
    - 09/19/1913
    - 10/10/1913
    - 10/17/1913
    - 11/07/1913
    - 11/14/1913
    - 11/21/1913
    - 11/28/1913
    - 12/05/1913
    - 12/12/1913
    - 12/19/1913
    - 05/01/1914
    - 06/05/1914
    - 06/19/1914
    - 07/03/1914
    - 08/06/1914
    - 09/04/1914
    - 10/09/1914
    - 11/20/1914
    - 12/04/1914
    - 01/01/1915
    - 02/05/1915
    - 03/12/1915
    - 03/26/1915
    - 04/02/1915
    - 04/09/1915
    - 05/14/1915
    - 05/21/1915
    - 06/18/1915
    - 07/02/1915
    - 07/09/1915
    - 07/23/1915
    - 07/30/1915
    - 08/06/1915
    - 10/15/1915
    - 10/22/1915
    - 11/05/1915
    - 01/14/1916
    - 01/28/1916
    - 02/04/1916
    - 02/11/1916
    - 02/18/1916
    - 02/25/1916
    - 03/03/1916
    - 03/24/1916
    - 04/07/1916
    - 04/14/1916
    - 04/21/1916
    - 04/28/1916
    - 05/05/1916
    - 05/26/1916
    - 06/09/1916
    - 06/16/1916
    - 07/07/1916
    - 07/14/1916
    - 07/28/1916
    - 08/04/1916
    - 08/11/1916
    - 08/18/1916
    - 08/24/1916
    - 09/01/1916
    - 09/08/1916
    - 09/15/1916
    - 09/22/1916
    - 09/29/1916
    - 10/06/1916
    - 10/13/1916
    - 10/20/1916
    - 10/27/1916
    - 11/24/1916
    - 12/08/1916
    - 12/22/1916
    - 08/03/1917
    - 10/26/1917
    - 11/02/1917
    - 11/09/1917
    - 11/16/1917
    - 11/23/1917
    - 12/14/1917
    - 01/04/1918
    - 02/15/1918
    - 03/01/1918
    - 03/08/1918
    - 03/15/1918
    - 03/29/1918
    - 04/12/1918
    - 04/19/1918
    - 05/24/1918
    - 05/31/1918
    - 06/07/1918
    - 06/14/1918
    - 06/21/1918
    - 06/28/1918
    - 07/05/1918
    - 07/12/1918
    - 07/20/1918
    - 08/02/1918
    - 08/09/1918
    - 08/30/1918
    - 09/06/1918
    - 09/13/1918
    - 09/20/1918
    - 09/27/1918
    - 11/15/1918
    - 11/22/1918
    - 11/29/1918
    - 12/06/1918
    - 12/13/1918
    - 12/20/1918
    - 01/03/1919
    - 01/10/1919
    - 01/17/1919
    - 06/04/1943
    - 06/11/1943
    - 06/16/1943
    - 06/25/1943
    - 07/02/1943
    - 07/09/1943
    - 07/22/1953
    - 07/30/1943
    - 08/06/1943
    - 08/13/1943
    - 08/20/1943
    - 08/27/1943
    - 09/03/1943
    - 09/10/1943
    - 09/17/1943
    - 09/24/1943
    - 10/01/1943
    - 10/08/1943
    - 10/15/1943
    - 10/22/1943
    - 10/29/1943
    - 11/05/1943
    - 11/12/1943
    - 11/19/1943
    - 11/26/1943
    - 12/03/1943
    - 12/10/1943
    - 12/17/1943
    - 12/24/1943
    - 01/07/1944
    - 01/11/1944
    - 01/21/1944
    - 01/28/1944
    - 02/04/1944
    - 02/18/1944
    - 03/03/1944
    - 03/10/1944
    - 03/17/1944
    - 03/24/1944
    - 03/31/1944
    - 04/21/1944
    - 05/12/1944
    - 05/19/1944
    - 06/02/1944
    - 06/16/1944
    - 07/14/1944
    - 07/21/1944
    - 07/28/1944
    - 08/04/1944
    - 08/11/1944
    - 08/18/1944
    - 08/25/1944
    - 09/08/1944
    - 09/22/1944
    - 09/29/1944
    - 10/06/1944
    - 10/13/1944
    - 10/20/1944
    - 10/27/1944
    - 11/03/1944
    - 11/10/1944
    - 11/17/1944
    - 12/08/1944
    - 12/15/1944
    - 12/22/1944
    - 01/05/1945
    - 01/12/1945
    - 01/19/1945
    - 01/26/1945
    - 02/09/1945
    - 02/16/1945
    - 03/02/1945
    - 03/09/1945
    - 05/11/1945
    - 08/31/1945
    - 09/07/1945
    - 10/12/1945
    - 06/07/1946
    - 08/02/1946
    - 08/09/1946
    - 08/16/1946
    - 08/30/1946
    - 01/31/1947
    - 02/07/1947
    - 03/07/1947
- Box 8: McKenry-Peterburg (Not Narrows) (Box 8)
  - Midland Virginian, Palmyra, VA
    - 04/07/1898, 3, 50
  - Norfolk Herald (The), Norfolk, VA
    - 07/05/1890, XII, 31
    - 0712/1890, XII, 32
  - Norfolk Landmark (The), Norfolk, VA
    - 10/22/1889, XXIX, 144
    - 05/16/1901
    - 05/17/1901-05/19/1901, LII, no. 70-72
    - 07/19/1901, LII, 124
  - Norfolk Weekly Herald (The), Norfolk, VA
    - 07/19/1890, XIII, 1
    - 07/26/1890
    - 08/02/1890
    - 08/09/1890
    - 08/16/1890
    - 08/23/1890
    - 08/30/1890
  - Pearisburg Gazette, Pearisburg, VA
    - 01/31/1874, VIII, 16
    - 12/03/1880, XIV, 47
    - 01/14/1881, XV, 2
    - 01/28/1881, XV, 4
    - 08/12/1881, XV, 31
    - 06/30/1882, XVI, 25
    - 07/14/1882, XVI, 27
    - 07/21/1882, XVI, 28
    - 10/12/1901, XXXVIII, 21
    - 01/25/1923, LXIV, 4
  - Petersburg Index and Appeal, Petersburg, VA
    - 12/18/1873, 83
  - Pulaski People (The), Newbern, VA
    - 08/14/1884, XIII, 645
    - 08/21/1884, XIII, 646
    - 12/18/1884, XIII, 663
  - School and Tariff Advocate (The), Petersburg, VA
    - 09/24/1889
  - South and West, Mechanicsburg, VA
    - 04/05/1879, II, 24
    - 07/08/1880, III, 33
  - Southern Times (The), Norfolk, VA
    - 11/02/1889, I, 14
  - Virginian-Pilot, Norfolk, VA
    - 09/07/1899, III, 137
    - 09/08/1899, 138
    - 09/19/1899-09/29/1899, III, no. 147-156
    - 10/01/1899-10/05/1899, IV, no. 158-161
    - 10/08/1899-10/10/1899, IV, no. 164-165
- Box 9: Narrows (Box 9)
  - Narrow News (The), Narrows, VA
    - 08/17/1939-05/09/1940, 1, no. 14- 52
    - 05/23/1940-05/15/1941, 2, no. 2- 54
    - 05/22/1941-06/11/1942, 3, no. 1-53
- Box 10: Pulaski-Radford (Box 10)
  - Montgomery Democrat, Radford, VA
    - 04/25/1890-05/02/1890, IV, 20-21
  - News Journal (The), Radford, VA
    - 04/28/1961, 78, 20
  - News-Review (The), Pulaski, VA
    - 05/31/1901
  - Radford Advance, Radford, VA
    - 05/24/1901, 10, 22
  - Radford News (The), Radford, VA
    - 01/08/1925, XIII, 12
    - 01/15/1925, XIII, 19
  - Radford Plant Weekly, Radford, VA
    - 11/13/1940-12/11/1940, 1, no. 1-5
    - 12/24/1940-02/05/1941, 1, no. 7-13
    - 02/12/1941-06/25/1941, 2, no. 1 -20
    - 07/10/1941-09/04/1941, 3, no. 1-9
  - Southwest Times (The), Pulaski, VA
    - 09/01/1942-09/09/1942, 37, 164-171
    - 09/11/1942-09/25/1942, 37, 173- 185
    - 12/31/1942-01/08/1943, 37, 266-273
    - 01/11/1943-02/21/1943, 37, 275-310
  - Virginia People (The), Pulaski County, VA
    - 05/09/1873, II, 19
    - 05/23/1873, II, 21
    - 09/26/1873, II, 39
    - 07/23/1874, III, 23
    - 08/30/1876, V, 35
    - 02/07/1878, VII, 5
    - 08/04/1881, X, 29
- Boxes 11, 13, 14, 16: Richmond (Box 11, Box 13, Box 14, Box 16)
  - Campaign (The), Richmond, VA
    - 06/07/1884, I, 42
    - 07/19/1884, I, 48
    - 09/12/1885, III, 2
  - Commonwealth (The), Richmond, VA
    - 01/30/1880, I, 1
    - 06/19/1880, I, 123
  - Daily Dispatch (Richmond Dispatch), Richmond, VA
    Note
    Please note: All but one of the 1861 and 1862 issues (materials in Box 16) are reprints, not originals.
    - 04/13/1861, XIX, 86 (Box 16)
    - 04/15/1861, XIX, 87 (Box 16)
    - 04/16/1861, XIX, 88 (Box 16)
    - 04/17/1861, XIX, 89 (Box 16)
    - 04/18/1861, XIX, 90 (Box 16)
    - 04/19/1861, XIX, 91 (Box 16)
    - 04/20/1861, XIX, 91 (Box 16)
    - 04/22/1861, XIX, 92 (Box 16)
    - 04/23/1861, XIX, 93 (Box 16)
    - 04/24/1861, XIX, 94 (Box 16)
    - 04/25/1861, XIX, 95 (Box 16)
    - 04/26/1861, XIX, 96 (Box 16)
    - 04/27/1861, XIX, 97 (Box 16)
    - 04/29/1861, XIX, 97 (Box 16)
    - 04/30/1861, XIX, 98 (Box 16)
    - 05/01/1861, XIX, 99 (Box 16)
    - 05/02/1861, XIX, 100 (Box 16)
    - 05/03/1861, XIX, 101 (Box 16)
    - 05/04/1861, XIX, 102 (Box 16)
    - 05/06/1861, XIX, 103 (Box 16)
    - 05/07/1861, XIX, 104 (Box 16)
    - 05/08/1861, XIX, 105 (Box 16)